mystorybook.com 2016-04-08

# My Storybook

**myStorybook.com** takes you and your children's privacy seriously.

By accepting the Privacy Policy in registration or by visiting and using the Site, you expressly consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to our Terms of Service.

This is the Privacy Policy of the MyStorybook.com website (the “Site”) (“MyStorybook”, “us”, “our” and “we” and terms of similar meaning). It describes the information that we collect from you as part of the normal operation of our Site, and how we use and disclose that information.

In this Privacy Policy, we use the term “Member” to describe a registered user of the Site. Together with Members, people who browse our Site without becoming Members are called “Users” of our Site.

## Information That We Collect

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information from you is to provide functionality and features that improve your experience, and make our service safer and easier to use. We do our best to only collect personal information about you that we consider necessary for that.

In most cases, you can browse the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you become a Member, we require you to provide various contact and identity information and other personal information as indicated on the relevant forms on the Site, and you are no longer anonymous to us. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to become a Member or by not using the particular feature of the Site for which the information is being collected. Remember that if you include personal information in your stories we have access to that information as well.

We also automatically track certain information about you based upon your behaviour on our Site. We use this information to do internal research on our users’ demographics, interests, and behaviour to better understand, protect and serve you and our community. 

“Cookies” are small files delivered to your computer that assist us in providing our services. Cookies will be used on the Site to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session, to help us with data collection on the Site to help analyze our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety, to offer certain features that are only available through the use of a cookie and to allow us to provide information that is targeted to your interests. Cookies are very commonly used on the internet, and if you have cookies disabled in your browser you may not be able to use the Site properly.

If you send us personal correspondence, such as questions or other emails, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities on the Site, we may collect and/or keep such information.

Once you become a member, you can review and change your information on your account page.

## How We Use Your Information

We use personal information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site, to provide to you the services offered by the Site; resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our Terms of Service; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection, use or disclosure. We may compare and review your personal information for errors, omissions and for accuracy. We may also use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze Site usage, to improve our content and product offerings, and to customize the Site’s content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Site.

We may also use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as MyStorybook promotions, learning resources, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. If you do not wish to receive these communications, you can opt out of the receipt of certain communications within the email body or on your account page of the Site. You may make changes to your account preferences at any time.

## Our Disclosure of Your Information

We will not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties without your explicit consent. The following describes some of the ways that your personal information may be disclosed in the normal scope of business to provide our services.

Username. The username you choose, and your avatar (if applicable) will be publicly viewable both on the site, and anywhere else on the internet that the book is visible. This includes (but is not limited to) storybook comments, forum discussions, and anywhere your stories are shared.

Stories. In the normal operation of the Site, if you choose to make a storybook public, information you include in your stories will be visible to anyone. 

In some cases we may provide your personal information to third party vendors and suppliers that we engage to help us provide services to our users. For example, we may engage third parties to process your payments, solicit feedback, produce or ship products and other goods or services that you order from us. If you don't want to provide this information to third parties, you may in some cases choose to not use the features that require third party services. If you have specific concerns around this, please contact us for details. 

## Legal Requests and Emergencies

We cooperate with law enforcement inquiries and demands for information that are made under force of law. Therefore, we may provide personal information to law enforcement agencies in what we believe to be emergency situations, we may provide personal information where we have a good-faith belief that we are required to do so by statute, court order, legal process or lawful authority, and we may provide it to our legal counsel in connection with the foregoing. We may also disclose personal information to third parties if we believe, in good faith, that disclosure is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Service, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend ourself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our web site, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of MyStorybook, our users or others. In some cases, personal information that we collect may be stored or processed outside of Canada, and may therefore be subject to the legal jurisdiction of those countries.

## Sale or Financing

If MyStorybook becomes involved in a proposed amalgamation or sale of some or all of its assets, or if its owners propose to sell their interest in the company, or in the course of a proposed financing, we may disclose personal information to the proposed acquirors or investors, and their advisors, as part of their due diligence investigations of the Company or upon the completion of the applicable transaction. Any such disclosure will be pursuant to confidentiality agreements customary for such transactions.

## Effective Date, Updates and Acceptance

This Privacy Policy is effective as of July 2014. Your use of the Site and services on the Site is subject to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service. Your use of this Site and/or the services on the Site, shall be deemed your acceptance of the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If so, we will post our updated Privacy Policy on this page and post notice of the change. Your continued use of any portion of the Site and/or services on the Site following posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.

Questions?

We want you to feel comfortable with how we handle your private information. Please contact us if you have any questions, concerns or if you would like more detailed information.
